

VITALIY BONDARENKO Junior Java Developer

# **ABOUT ME**

Innovative and deadline-driven Software Developer with 15+ years of experience design and development user-centered software from initial concept stage to the final, polished functional deliverable

Citizenship: Ukraine



June 7, 1981 in Ukraine



vibondarenko@gmail.com



vibondarenko.github.io



+43 68181292782



Mühlstraße 42b, 11 4600 Wels, Austria

# LANGUAGES

**Ukrainian:** Native **Russian:** Native **English:** B1

**Deutsch:** A1 – in progress

# **SKILLS**

**Languages:** Delphi(Object Pascal), SQL, Java 8, JavaScript (basics), C++ (basics), C++ (Arduino), HTML + CSS (basics)

**Frameworks:** Spring, Spring MVC, Spring Security, Spring REST

**Tools:** Git, Maven

Databases: MS SQL Server, Oracle,

**PostgreSQL** 

**Operation systems:** Windows, Linux

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## 07.2014 - 03.2022

#### **DELPHI DEVELOPER**

Freelancer (Kyiv, Ukraine)

- Developed architecture and design of industrial weighing systems
- Developed and implemented software for truck, railway balances, weight indicators (indicators of Rice Lake Weighing Systems company)
- Developed software for weighing truck in motion
- Developed software for microcontrollers (Arduino)

#### $\bigcirc$ 12.2007 - 07.2014

#### **DELPHI DEVELOPER**

Metroves LTD (Kyiv, Ukraine) – Truck and Railway Balances Production

- Developed architecture and design of industrial weighing systems
- Developed and implemented software for truck, railway balances, weight indicators (indicators of Rice Lake Weighing Systems)
- Integrated with system of recognition truck and carriages numbers (Viinex)
- Integrated with different accounting systems at the enterprise

## **O**07.2007 – 10.2007

#### **DELPHI DEVELOPER**

Cybersystems LTD (Kyiv, Ukraine) – Software Development

Developed and tested software for television (project for 3 month)

#### **07.2006 - 07.2007**

# TERRASOFT CRM DEVELOPER

Information Agency "IBC" LTD (Donetsk, Ukraine) – Software Sales &

Integration

- Integrated and provided technical support of Terrasoft CRM
- Developed plugins and scripts for Terrasoft CRM

#### $\bigcirc$ 06.2004 - 07.2006

#### **DELPHI DEVELOPER**

**TK-Donbass LTD** (Donetsk, Ukraine) – Textile Factory

- Developed, implemented, maintained automatized calculation subsystems for the enterprise
- Developed the client section of the client-server application

#### **EDUCATION & COURSES**

#### $\bigcirc$ 01.05.2022 - 15.05.2022

#### **JAVA SPRING FOR BEGINNERS**

#### **Udemy.com**

– 20 hours of theory and practice Java Spring Framework (IoC and DI, AOP, Hibernate basics, Spring MVC, Spring REST, Spring Security, Spring Boot)

## **EDUCATION & COURSES (Continue)**

#### **12.2015 – 02.2016**

#### **JAVA 8 (JUNIOR JAVA DEVELOPER)**

Brain Academy (Main Academy, mainacademy.ua) (Kyiv, Ukraine)

- 120 hours of theory and practice Java (Java Fundamentals, OOP, Exceptions, Generics, Collections, Multi-threading, OOD, Patterns, Reflections, IO Streams, Annotations and etc.)
- Course project: https://github.com/VIBondarenko/brainacadproject

#### 09.2002 - 01.2004

## **Master of Specialized Computer Systems in medicine**

**Faculty of Computer Information Technologies and Automatics Donetsk National Technical University** (Donetsk (now in Lutsk), Ukraine)

Diploma Thesis: The expert system using fuzzy logic for lungs diagnostic

#### $\bigcirc$ 09.1998 - 07.2002

## **Bachelor of Computer Engineering in medicine**

**Faculty of Computer Information Technologies and Automatics Donetsk National Technical University** (Donetsk (now in Lutsk), Ukraine)

Studied: Discrete Math, Probability Theory, Database Management Systems, Object Oriented Programming, Automatic Control Theory, Human Anatomy, Pathology Fundamentals, Human Diagnostic Fundamentals, Computer Diagnostic Systems Design and etc.